(SENSUAL MUSIC)
♪ I'VE BEEN REALLY
TRYING, BABY ♪
♪ TRYIN' TO HOLD BACK
THIS FEELING FOR SO LONG ♪
♪ AND IF YOU FEEL
LIKE I FEEL, BABY ♪
♪ THEN, C'MON,
OH, C'MON, WHOO ♪
♪ LET'S GET IT
ON, AH, BABY ♪
♪ LET'S GET IT ON ♪
♪ LET'S LOVE, BABY ♪
♪ LET'S GET IT ON, SUGAR ♪
♪ LET'S GET IT ON ♪
♪ WOO HOO ♪
♪ WE'RE ALL
SENSITIVE PEOPLE ♪
♪ WITH SO MUCH TO GIVE ♪
♪ UNDERSTAND ME, SUGAR ♪
♪ OOH, OOH SINCE WE'VE GOT
TO BE HERE ♪
♪ LET'S LIVE ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH ME ♪
♪ LOVING YOU, BABY NO NO ♪
♪ AND GIVING YOURSELF TO
ME CAN NEVER BE WRONG ♪
♪ IF THE LOVE IS
TRUE, OH BABY ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW HOW
SWEET AND WONDERFUL ♪
♪ LIFE CAN BE ♪
♪ OOH LET ME LOVE YOU ♪
♪ I'M ASKING YOU BABY ♪
♪ TO GET IT ON WITH ME ♪
♪ OOH OOH LET ME LOVE YOU ♪
♪ OOH LET ME LOVE YOU ♪
♪ I AIN'T GONNA WORRY
LET ME LOVE YOU ♪
♪ I AIN'T GONNA PUSH
♪ WON'T PUSH YOU,
BABY LET ME LOVE YOU ♪
♪ SO C'MON, C'MON, C'MON,
C'MON, C'MON, BABY ♪
♪ STOP BEATIN' 'ROUND
THE BUSH, HEY ♪
♪ LET'S GET IT
ON, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ LET'S GET IT ON ♪
♪ OOH, OOH YOU KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT I'M TALKIN' BOUT ♪
♪ C'MON, BABY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ LET YOUR LOVE COME OUT ♪
♪ IF YOU BELIEVE IN
LOVE, LET'S GET IT ON ♪
♪ OOH, LET'S GET
IT ON, BABY ♪
♪ THIS MINUTE, OH
YEAH, LET'S GET IT ON ♪
♪ PLEASE ♪
♪ PLEASE GET IT ON ♪
♪ AH I KNOW AND YOU KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT I'VE BEEN
DREAMING OF ♪
♪ DON'T YOU BABY
AH, AH, AH, AH ♪
♪ I GOTTA HOLD YA
MY WHOLE BODY ♪
♪ MY BODY WANTS YA, BABY
MAKES THAT FEELIN' OF LOVE ♪
♪ I'M HAPPY MY
BODY WANTS YA ♪
♪ I AIN'T GONNA WORRY,
NO I AIN'T GONNA PUSH ♪
♪ I WON'T PUSH
YOU BABY, WOO ♪
♪ C'MON, C'MON, C'MON,
C'MON, C'MON, DARLIN' ♪
♪ STOP BEATIN'
'ROUND THE BUSH ♪
♪ OH, GONNA GET IT
ON OOH, OOH ♪
♪ THREATENIN' YOU, BABY
OOH, OOH ♪
♪ I WANNA GET
IT ON OOH, OOH ♪
♪ YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY THAT IT'S WRONG ♪
♪ IF THE SPIRIT MOVES YA,
LET ME GROOVE YA GOOD ♪
♪ LET YOUR LOVE
COME DOWN, OH ♪
♪ GET IT ON ♪
♪ C'MON, BABY ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW THE MEANING ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN SANCTIFIED ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, GIRL, YOU
GIVE ME GOOD FEELING ♪
♪ SO GOOD, SOMETHIN'
LIKE SANCTIFIED ♪
♪ OH DEAR I, BABY ♪
♪ NOTHING WRONG WITH LOVE ♪
♪ IF YOU WANT TO LOVE ME
JUST LET YOUR SELF GO ♪
♪ OH BABY, LET'S GET IT ON ♪